export default {
  id: 'low_1006_4_2b',
  name: '상용한자(4학년-2/한자찾기)',
  data: [
    { question: '독:な(る)、な(す)/음:せい、じょう', answer: ['成'] },
    { question: '독:はぶ(く)、かえり(みる)/음:せい、しょう', answer: ['省'] },
    { question: '독:す/음:そう', answer: ['巣'] },
    { question: '독:や(く)、や(ける)/음:しょう', answer: ['焼'] },
    { question: '독:わら(う)、え(む)/음:しょう', answer: ['笑'] },
    { question: '독:たば/음:そく', answer: ['束'] },
    { question: '독:つづ(く)、つづ(ける)/음:ぞく', answer: ['続'] },
    { question: '독:まご/음:そん', answer: ['孫'] },
    { question: '독:まつ/음:しょう', answer: ['松'] },
    { question: '독:す(る)/음:さつ', answer: ['刷'] },
    { question: '독:순할/음:じゅん', answer: ['順'] },
    { question: '독:ため(す)、こころ(みる)/음:し', answer: ['試'] },
    { question: '독:신하/음:しん、じん', answer: ['臣'] },
    { question: '독:믿을/음:しん', answer: ['信'] },
    { question: '독:うしなう/음:しつ', answer: ['失'] },
    { question: '독:うじ/음:し', answer: ['氏'] },
    { question: '독:め/음:が', answer: ['芽'] },
    { question: '독:아이/음:じ、に', answer: ['児'] },
    { question: '독:책상/음:あん', answer: ['案'] },
    { question: '독:사랑/음:あい', answer: ['愛'] },
    { question: '독:맺을/음:やく', answer: ['約'] },
    { question: '독:やしな(う)/음:よう', answer: ['養'] },
    { question: '독:고기 잡을/음:ぎょ、りょう', answer: ['漁'] },
    { question: '독:억/음:おく', answer: ['億'] },
    { question: '독:그럴/음:ぜん、ねん', answer: ['然'] },
    { question: '독:あつ(い)/음:ねつ', answer: ['熱'] },
    { question: '독:しお/음:えん', answer: ['塩'] },
    { question: '독:꽃부리/음:えい', answer: ['英'] },
    { question: '독:さか(える)、は(え)、は(える)/음:えい', answer: ['栄'] },
    { question: '독:재주/음:げい', answer: ['芸'] },
    { question: '독:완전할/음:かん', answer: ['完'] },
    { question: '독:かなめ、い(る)/음:よう', answer: ['要'] },
    { question: '독:あ(びる)、あ(びせる)/음:よく', answer: ['浴'] },
    { question: '독:いさ(む)/음:ゆう', answer: ['勇'] },
    { question: '독:ねが(う)/음:がん', answer: ['願'] },
    { question: '독:くらい/음:い', answer: ['位'] },
    { question: '독:かこ(む)、かこ(う)/음:い', answer: ['囲'] },
    { question: '독:밥통/음:い', answer: ['胃'] },
    { question: '독:な(く)/음:きゅう', answer: ['泣'] },
    { question: '독:ころも/음:い', answer: ['衣'] },
    { question: '독:의논할/음:ぎ', answer: ['議'] },
    { question: '독:써/음:い', answer: ['以'] },
    { question: '독:しるし/음:いん', answer: ['印'] },
    { question: '독:어제/음:さく', answer: ['昨'] },
    { question: '독:のこ(る)、のこ(す)/음:ざん', answer: ['残'] },
    { question: '독:창자/음:ちょう', answer: ['腸'] },
    { question: '독:재목/음:ざい', answer: ['材'] },
    { question: '독:あらそ(う)/음:そう', answer: ['争'] },
    { question: '독:쌓을/음:ちょ', answer: ['貯'] },
    { question: '독:ひく(い)、ひく(める)、ひく(まる)/음:てい', answer: ['低'] },
    { question: '독:そこ/음:てい', answer: ['底'] },
    { question: '독:つ(む)、つ(もる)/음:せき', answer: ['積'] },
    { question: '독:まと/음:てき', answer: ['的'] },
    { question: '독:법/음:てん', answer: ['典'] },
    { question: '독:いくさ、たたか(う)/음:せん', answer: ['戦'] },
    { question: '독:つた(わる)、つた(える)、つた(う)/음:でん', answer: ['伝'] },
    { question: '독:お(る)、お(れる)、おり/음:せつ', answer: ['折'] },
    { question: '독:ふし/음:せつ、せち', answer: ['節'] },
    { question: '독:しず、しず(か)、しず(まる)、しず(める)/음:せい、じょう', answer: ['静'] },
    { question: '독:머무를/음:てい', answer: ['停'] },
    { question: '독:きざ(す)、きざ(し)/음:ちょう', answer: ['兆'] },
    { question: '독:て(る)、て(らす)、て(れる)/음:しょう', answer: ['照'] },
    { question: '독:마칠/음:そつ', answer: ['卒'] },
    { question: '독:たね/음:しゅ', answer: ['種'] },
    { question: '독:まわ(り)/음:しゅう', answer: ['周'] },
    { question: '독:なか/음:ちゅう', answer: ['仲'] },
    { question: '독:さ(す)/음:さ', answer: ['差'] },
    { question: '독:か(りる)/음:しゃく', answer: ['借'] },
    { question: '독:ふだ/음:さつ', answer: ['札'] },
    { question: '독:살필/음:さつ', answer: ['察'] },
    { question: '독:まい(る)/음:さん', answer: ['参'] },
    { question: '독:とな(える)/음:しょう', answer: ['唱'] },
    { question: '독:くら/음:そう', answer: ['倉'] },
    { question: '독:な/음:さい', answer: ['菜'] },
    { question: '독:あさ(い)/음:せん', answer: ['浅'] },
    { question: '독:きよ(い)、きよ(まる)、きよ(める)/음:せい、しょう', answer: ['清'] },
    { question: '독:はじ(め)、はじ(めて)、はつ、うい、そ(める)/음:しょ', answer: ['初'] },
    { question: '독:もっと(も)/음:さい', answer: ['最'] },
    { question: '독:いわ(う)/음:しゅく、しゅう', answer: ['祝'] },
    { question: '독:がわ/음:そく', answer: ['側'] },
    { question: '독:おさ(める)、おさ(まる)、なお(る)、なお(す)/음:じ、ち', answer: ['治'] },
    { question: '독:お(く)/음:ち', answer: ['置'] },
    { question: '독:특별할/음:とく', answer: ['特'] },
    { question: '독:やぶ(れる)/음:はい', answer: ['敗'] },
    { question: '독:たよ(り)/음:べん、びん', answer: ['便'] },
    { question: '독:つつ(む)/음:ほう', answer: ['包'] },
    { question: '독:표/음:ひょう', answer: ['票'] },
    { question: '독:표할/음:ひょう', answer: ['標'] },
    { question: '독:かなら(ず)/음:ひつ', answer: ['必'] },
    { question: '독:배/음:こう', answer: ['航'] },
    { question: '독:해할/음:がい', answer: ['害'] },
    { question: '독:시험/음:けん、げん', answer: ['験'] },
    { question: '독:화합할/음:きょう', answer: ['協'] },
    { question: '독:かた/음:けい', answer: ['型'] },
    { question: '독:この(む)、す(く)/음:こう', answer: ['好'] },
    { question: '독:재물/음:か', answer: ['貨'] },
    { question: '독:そうろう/음:こう', answer: ['候'] },
    { question: '독:가르칠/음:くん', answer: ['訓'] },
    { question: '독:바랄/음:き', answer: ['希'] },
    { question: '독:よろこ(ぶ)/음:き', answer: ['喜'] }

  ]
}
